Daniel Gizzi Diaz

Front-End Developer

+56 985083952 danielgizzidiaz@gmail.com Rancagua, Chile in/daniel-gizzi pgithub.com/danixcabe

Summary

I am a Computer Engineer with more than 4 years of experience as a Frontend Developer, focused on the development of friendly interfaces and a pleasant user experience. I have experience working in multidisciplinary teams and under agile methodologies. In addition, I have experience in different technologies such as, React, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, SASS, Redux, HTML5, Git, etc.

Professional Experience

Front-End Developer, (Entel)

Santiago, Chile 11/2023 - present

- Develop reusable components, ensuring best practices, improving website performance and always focused on providing a good user experience
- Support teammates in making decisions when a new development is to be carried out.
- Collaborate effectively with other teams such as Design, Backend and QA.
- Propose and implement new features to improve Entel's website.

Front-End Developer, (Multiplica Talent)

Santiago, Chile 08/2022 - 10/2023

- Develop reusable components, ensuring best practices, improving website performance and always focused on providing a good user experience
- Support teammates in making decisions when a new development is to be carried out.
- Collaborate effectively with other teams such as Design, Backend and QA.
- Propose and implement new features to improve Entel's website.

Web Developer, (O'Higgins University)

Rancagua, Chile 07/2019 - 07/2022

- Planning and execution of promotional events to increase brand awareness.
- Collaboration with internal teams and external suppliers to ensure the successful execution of events.
- Evaluation of the effectiveness of activations by analyzing customer participation and feedback.

Education

Informatic Engineer INACAP

Rancagua, Chile 2020-2021

Cursos Relevantes: Software y Hardware, Web Development, Data Base y Mobile Development

Analyst Programmer INACAP

Rancagua, Chile 2017-2019

Cursos Relevantes: Software y Hardware, Web Development, Data Base y Mobile Development

Skills

• Software: React JS, Git, JavaScript, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, HTML5, SASS, Kanban, Scrum, Jira.

Languages

• English [Intermediate]

• Spanish [Native]